#### **KEVIN GRANADOS**

# 3033 Madame Plantier ave, North Las Vegas, NV 89081 C: (702)426-7416 E: kevingranados@ymail.com

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Results-oriented Electrical Engineering Student specializing in high-level problem solving, process efficiency and day-to-day

Maintenance in a manufacturing environment.

Power tools	SKI	SKILLS		Highly Reliable	
Microsoft Office		Quick learner			
Time management		Strong client relations		client relations	
Machinery (Forklift)	Traini		ainin	g development aptitude	
Technical support			Cash flow management		
Advanced critical thinking		Intermediate Linux			
Operation system software	Self-m		elf-m	otivated	
Creative problem solver				Superb Communication	
	WORK HISTORY				

## Photographer, 03/2019 to Current

## Independent Freelance Work – Las Vegas, NV

- Capture high resolution raw footage with camera
- Develop photos in post production
- Correct lighting and color to maximize image quality
- Consolidate Clients photos in folder to send off
- Fluent in Adobe Photoshop/Lightroom

\_

## MarketSource Target - Mobile Sale Representative 02/2016 - 11/2016

- Check receiving for new phone shipments
- Add new phones to registry
- Count daily inventory
- Assist customers with new carrier plans
- Pitch new sales for ongoing promotions
- verify trade-ins and place trade-in orders for shipments

# Rakuten Super Logistics - Receiving Specialist 11/2016 - 10/2017

- Receive all daily merchandise from local carriers FedEx, UPS, DHL, etc.
- Sign off any BoL's (Bill of Lading) from trucks/containers with accurate pallet count
- Start a kitting/separation process with all like items
- Process inventory counts on arrived merchandise
- Match corrected counts with packing slip (If provided)
- Input all counts into system for an updated inventory
- Put away all items that have successfully been counted and re-counted
- Edit any issues that may have occurred during count process discrepancies, overages and extras

#### TCSJohnHuxley - Gaming Technician/ Systems Administration 10/2016 - Current

- Performs installations, diagnostics and corrective procedures.
- Performs installations and repair procedures with limited direct supervision
- Must be able to troubleshoot and repair all technical product issues
- Communicate using Sales Force to provide status of service call
- Maintains and secures assigned tools, test equipment, parts and supplies
- Responsible for maintaining stock in vehicle with sufficient inventory of parts and other items required for service call
- Responds timely to all service calls assigned by Salesforce or Manager
- Maintain service history information including repairs and service visits using Salesforce
- Conduct preventative maintenance (PM's)
- Follows defined escalation procedures in reporting problems or repair issues using Salesforce
- Maintain scheduled maintenance on company vehicle and report and damage pr accidents

- Must comply with all Occupational Safety & Heath Administration (OSHA) safety procedures and any additional state licensing regulations as applicable
- Responsible for the maintenance, configuration, and reliable operation of computer systems, network servers, and virtualization
- Install and upgrade computer components and software, manage virtual servers, and integrate automation processes
- Troubleshoot hardware and software errors by running diagnostics, documenting problems and resolutions, prioritizing problems, and assessing impact of issues
- Provide documentation and technical specifications to IT staff for planning and implementing new or upgrades of IT infrastructure
- Perform or delegate regular backup operations and implement appropriate processes for data protection, disaster recovery, and failover procedures
- Lead desktop and helpdesk support efforts, making sure all desktop applications, workstations, and related equipment problems are resolved in a timely manner with limited disruptions
- Responsible for capacity, storage planning, and database performance

#### **EDUCATION**

Associate of Applied Science: Electronics Engineering Technology, Graduated: 3/2015

ITT Technical Institute - North Las Vegas, NV

Academic Achievement Awards of Highest Honors & Perfect Attendance

#### **RELEVANT COURSEWORK**

Computer Structure and Logic

**DC-AC Electronics** 

Microprocessors and Micro-controllers

**Programmable Logic Controllers** 

**Physics** 

**Integrated Circuits** 

**Electronic Communications** 

Networking